discountasp.net 2019-08-07

# DiscountASP.NET policies

This Privacy Policy applies to DiscountASP.NET owned and operated by Host Collective, Inc. DiscountASP.NET (we, us, our) understands that the privacy of your data is important to our customers (you, your, Client). This Privacy Policy sets out how we collect and use certain information that our customers have told us is important to them. This Privacy Policy covers web sites with the URL www.discountasp.net that are managed by DiscountASP.NET and used to market services or provide support for services. 

This Privacy Policy covers our collection, use and disclosure of information we collect through our service. The use of information collected through our service shall be limited to the purpose of providing the service for which the Client has engaged DiscountASP.NET. 

**EU-U.S. Privacy Shield and Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield**

DiscountASP.NET and its parent company Host Collective, Inc. and subsidiary company, Everleap, participates in and has certified its compliance with the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework and the Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework. We are committed to subjecting all personal data received from European Union (EU) member countries and Switzerland, respectively, in reliance on each Privacy Shield Framework, to the Framework’s applicable Principles. To learn more about the Privacy Shield Frameworks, and to view our certification, visit the [U.S. Department of Commerce’s Privacy Shield List](https://www.privacyshield.gov/list).

DiscountASP.NET and its parent company Host Collective, Inc. and subsidiary company, Everleap, complies with the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework and the Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework (Privacy Shield) as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information transferred from the European Union and the United Kingdom and/or Switzerland, to the United States in reliance on Privacy Shield. DiscountASP.NET and its parent company Host Collective, Inc. and subsidiary company, Everleap, has certified to the Department of Commerce that it adheres to the Privacy Shield Principles with respect to such information. If there is any conflict between the terms in this privacy policy and the Privacy Shield Principles, the Privacy Shield Principles shall govern. To learn more about the Privacy Shield program, and to view our certification, please visit [privacyshield.gov](https://www.privacyshield.gov/). 

DiscountASP.NET is responsible for the processing of personal data it receives, under the Privacy Shield Framework, and subsequently transfers to a third party acting as an agent on its behalf. DiscountASP.NET complies with the Privacy Shield Principles for all onward transfers of personal data from the EU and Switzerland, including the onward transfer liability provisions.

With respect to personal data received or transferred pursuant to the Privacy Shield Framework, DiscountASP.NET is subject to the regulatory enforcement powers of the U.S. Federal Trade Commission. In certain situations, DiscountASP.NET may be required to disclose personal data in response to lawful requests by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements.

If you have an unresolved privacy or data use concern that we have not addressed satisfactorily, please contact our U.S.-based third party dispute resolution provider (free of charge) at <https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request>.

Under certain conditions, more fully described on the [Privacy Shield website](https://www.privacyshield.gov/article?id=How-to-Submit-a-Complaint), you may invoke binding arbitration when other dispute resolution procedures have been exhausted.

**Information we collect**

**Order Information**

If you purchase a product or service from us, we request certain personally identifiable information from you on our order form (Order Information). For our web hosting services, you must first provide your domain name or a domain name you wish to purchase. Then we will collect your contact information (such as name, company, email, address and phone number) and financial information (such as credit card number, expiration date). We collect the same information for services that do not require a domain name. 

We collect information under the direction of its Clients, and has no direct relationship with the individuals whose personal data it processes. If you are a customer of one of our Clients and would no longer like to be contacted by one of our Clients that use our service, please contact the Client that you interact with directly. We may transfer personal information to companies that help us provide our service. Transfers to subsequent third parties are covered by the service agreements with our Clients. 

We use this information for billing purposes and to fill your orders, to market new products and services to you, and to send you general information (like newsletters) that we think you will be interested in. This Order Information may be aggregated to create an administrative record that includes information related to the products and services provided to you, how you use those services, problems related to the services and notations from our staff about our relationship with you, among other things. 

If we have trouble processing an order, we will use this information to contact you. 

**User Data Supplementation**

We may receive information about you from other sources, including publicly available databases or third parties from whom we have purchased data, and combine this data with information we already have about you. This helps us to update, expand and analyze our records, identify new customers, and provide products and services that may be of interest to you. If you provide us personal information about others, or if others give us your information, we will only use that information for the specific reason for which it was provided to us.

Examples of the types of personal information that may be obtained from public sources or purchased from third parties and combined with information we already have about you, may include purchased marketing data about our customers from third parties that is combined with information we already have about you, to create more tailored advertising and products

**Secure Registration Information Collection**

The security of your personally identifiable information is important to us. When you enter personally identifiable information as well as sensitive information (such as credit card number) on our registration or order forms and account management interfaces (like the control panel), we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). 

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personally identifiable information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personally identifiable information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. 

If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can email us at support@discountasp.net. 

**Data Retention**

We will retain your information and personal data we process on behalf of our Clients for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. If you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer provide you services contact us at billing@discountasp.net. We will retain your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements. 

**Statistical Information**

All of our servers collect statistical information such as your IP address, date you visited, computer you are using, and operating system, among other data (Statistical Information). We use this information to analyze trends and understand demographic information about our user base so that we can improve our services and usability of our services. 

We may use Statistical Information to operate our hardware and software, diagnose problems and administer our web site. We may also use aggregate information to modify the products and services we offer based on who is visiting our web site, and what they are purchasing.

**Third Party Products and Services**

We offer some products and services that are provided by third parties (Third Party Products). These Third Party Products may collect and use information in ways that differ from those set out in this Privacy Policy. We will provide you with links to the websites of the providers of Third Party Products on your written request. 

**Cookies**

We use cookies for our order form and control panel to remember users’ settings and for authentication. Users can control the use of cookies at the individual browser level. If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but your ability to use some features or areas of our site may be limited. 

**Tracking Technologies**

Technologies such as: cookies, beacons, tags and scripts are used by DiscountASP.NET and our marketing partners, affiliates, or analytics or security service providers. These technologies are used in analyzing trends, administering the site, tracking users’ movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We may receive reports based on the use of these technologies by these companies on an individual as well as aggregated basis.

**Analytics / Log files**

As is true of most web sites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information may include Internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and/or clickstream data. We do not link this automatically collected data to other information we collect about you. 

**Local Storage (HTML)**

Third parties with whom we partner to provide certain features on our site or to display advertising based upon your Web browsing activity use LSs such as HTML 5 to collect and store information. Various browsers may offer their own management tools for removing HTML5.

**Behavioral Targeting**

We partner with a third party to either display advertising on our Web site or to manage our advertising on other sites. Our third party partner may use technologies such as cookies to gather information about your activities on this site and other sites in order to provide you advertising based upon your browsing activities and interests. If you wish to not have this information used for the purpose of serving you interest-based ads, you may opt-out by clicking [here](https://preferences-mgr.truste.com/) (or if located in the European Union click [here](https://www.youronlinechoices.eu/)). Please note this does not opt you out of being served ads. You will continue to receive generic ads.

**Google AdSense/Adwords**

We use Google AdSense to advertise this site. When you view or click on an ad a cookie will be set to help better provide advertisements that may be of interest to you on other Web sites. You may opt-out of the use of this cookie by visiting [Google’s Advertising and Privacy page](https://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

**Choice/Opt-out**

We provide you the opportunity to ‘opt-out’ of having your personally identifiable information used for certain purposes. For example, if you purchase a product/service but do not wish to receive any additional marketing material from us, you may opt-out by following the unsubscribe link located at the bottom of each email. 

**Customer Inquiries**

If you contact us about a problem/issue or with a question, we may ask you for specific information related to this contact (Customer Inquiry Information). We use Customer Inquiry Information to identify you individually. It is used throughout our business to provide services to you. Customer Inquiry Information may be associated with your Order Information to provide services to you. Customer Inquiry Information is shared with third parties to identify and fix problems with services when we are not capable of doing so ourselves. For more information on who we may share your information with, please see the “Other Disclosures” section below. 

**Updating/Accessing/Amending/Correcting Personally Identifiable Information**

Upon request DiscountASP.NET will provide you with information about whether we hold any of your personal information. If your personally identifiable information changes, you may correct, update, or delete inaccuracies through the Control Panel located at [https://my.discountasp.net](https://my.discountasp.net/) for web hosting customers and at [https://mytfs.discountasp.net](https://mytfs.discountasp.net/) for Team Foundation Server hosting customers. If you are having trouble accessing the Control Panel, our customer support team can assist and they can be contacted at support@discountasp.net. We will respond to your request to access within a reasonable timeframe. 

DiscountASP.NET acknowledges that you have the right to access your personal information. DiscountASP.NET has no direct relationship with the individuals whose personal data it processes. If you are a customer of one of our Clients, and you seek to access, correct, amend, or delete inaccurate data, then direct your query to DiscountASP.NET’s Client (the data controller).

We will respond to requests for access within a reasonable timeframe.

**Other disclosures**

DiscountASP.NET does not share, sell, rent or trade your personally identifiable information with third parties other than as disclosed within this Privacy Policy.

**Agents/Service Providers**

In the course of providing the services to you, we use the services of third parties, such as credit card processing companies, to bill you for goods and services, a survey provider to send out surveys on our behalf, and a mass email provider to manage specific opt-in email lists. We also use a third party service provider software that we use to host our Support Portal. 

When you order a new domain name, we will share your name, address, email and phone number with our domain registrar partner as necessary for the third party to provide that service. 

In certain situations, DiscountASP.NET may be required to disclose personal data in response to lawful requests by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements. These third parties are prohibited from using your personally identifiable information for promotional purposes. We are required to comply with relevant laws, regulations and judicial orders. Information covered by this Privacy Policy, as well as other categories of information, may be disclosed to third parties if we determine that such a disclosure is required by law, such as to comply with a subpoena, judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our web site; when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety and the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request.

It is possible that we may need to provide personally identifiable information to third party vendors that we use in order to provide our services – for example, we provide Microsoft based web hosting. It is possible that should we encounter an issue or bug with Microsoft software that can only be resolved by Microsoft, we may need to share personally identifiable information with Microsoft in order to replicate, troubleshoot and resolve the issue. Similarly, we offer email services using SmarterTools SmarterMail product. It is possible that we could encounter an email issue that must be researched by SmarterTools in order to provide us with a resolution, thus requiring us to provide SmarterTools with personally identifiable information. In these situations, we first ask the customer if we can share personally identifiable information with the third party. 

**Business Transitions**

In the event DiscountASP.NET goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, your personally identifiable information will likely be among the assets transferred. You will be notified via email of any such change in ownership or control of your personally identifiable information. 

**Forum/Blog**

If you use our forum or blog you should be aware that any personally identifiable information you submit there can be read, collected, or used by other users of these forums, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. We are not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit in these forums. To request removal of your personally identifiable information from our blog or community forum, contact us at support@discountasp.net. In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personally identifiable information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why. 

**Forum Member Directory**

As a member of our Forum, depending on your activity, we may list you in our member directory only visible to other Forum Members. If you wish to request removal of your information from our Forum Member Directory, you can contact us at support@discountasp.net.

**Customer Testimonials**

We use customer testimonials on our web site, and in our printed promotional material, which may contain personally identifiable information. We do obtain the customer's consent via email prior to posting the testimonial. To request removal of your personally identifiable information from your submitted testimonial, contact us at support@discountasp.net. 

**Surveys**

We may use third parties to conduct surveys on our behalf. These surveys will be sent to your email address. Participation in these surveys is completely voluntary and the email contains an out-out option. 

We may use a third party service provider to conduct these surveys; that company is prohibited from using our users’ personally identifiable information for any other purpose. We will not share the personally identifiable information you provide through a contest or survey with other third parties unless we give you prior notice and the option to opt out.

**Research Information/Publications**

We do publish research information based on survey data. “Research information” may include research papers, “infographics,” white papers, blog posts, and similar academic or commercial writings. Such research papers may include aggregate data, but does not include any personally identifiable information. Should we include any personally identifiable information, we would first ask the customer.

**Single Sign-On**

You can log in to our site using sign-in services such as Facebook Connect or an Open ID provider. These services will authenticate your identity and provide you the option to share certain personally identifiable information with us such as your name and email address to pre-populate our sign up form. Services like Facebook Connect give you the option to post information about your activities on this Web site to your profile page to share with others within your network. 

**Social Media Widgets**

Our web site includes social media features, such as the Facebook Like button and widgets, such as the ShareThis button or interactive mini-programs that run on our site. These features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the feature to function properly. Social media features and widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our web site. Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it. 

**Changes in this Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes at https://www.discountasp.net/policies/privacy/, the control panel, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices. We reserve the right to modify this privacy policy at any time, so please review it frequently. Before we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you by email. 

**Contact Information**

DiscountASP.NET  
417 East Huntington Drive  
Suite 200  
Monrovia, CA 91016  

Last Update: March 25, 2019
